{
    "subject": "resource/Mishti",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Actor",
    "human_readable": "Mishti's occupation is Actor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8598934412002563,
            "question": "Is Mishti an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8379135131835938,
            "question": "What is Mishti's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8076589703559875,
            "question": "What is Mishti's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6386349201202393,
            "question": "What is Mishti's job title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5863198041915894,
            "question": "Mishti is known for being what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5208228230476379,
            "question": "What role does Mishti play in the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4790349006652832,
            "question": "Describe Mishti's work."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4703401029109955,
            "question": "What is Mishti's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43407297134399414,
            "question": "What kind of work does Mishti do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25774505734443665,
            "question": "What does Mishti do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mishti's occupation is Actor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8146_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work does Mishti do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8146_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Mishti's area of expertise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8146_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe Mishti's work.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8146_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8146_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple documents that mention Mishti as an actress, which confirms her occupation as an actor. For example, from file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8146/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt:\n\n\"Indrani Chakraborty, better known by her stage name, Mishti, is an Indian actress who predominantly appears in Telugu and Hindi films.\"\n\nand from file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8146/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt:\n\n\"She is an actress, known for Kaanchi (2014), Adam Joan (2017) and Great Grand Masti (2016).\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Mishti, an Indian film actress who has appeared in films such as \"Kaanchi: The Unbreakable\" and \"Chinnadana Nee Kosam.\" This supports the statement that her occupation is that of an actor."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}